(Leonard:)Suppose there are worse ways
to spend a Friday night.
(Leonard:)None come to mind.
(Sheldon:)Look at this stamp.
On what authority
(Sheldon:)are they permitted to
mutilate patrons as they enter?
(Amy:)I'm sure it'll wash off.
(Sheldon:)Little comfort tonight.
(Sheldon:)I look like a Hell's Angel.
(Amy:)There's Zack.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure this is
what you want to do?
It's not what I want to do;
(Amy:)it's what I have to do.
(Sheldon:)Go, Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Sheldon:)Follow your endocrine system.
(Amy:)Thank you, Sheldon.
You're a good friend.
(Sheldon:)Please don't drag this out.
(Sheldon:)This is never going to come off.
(Amy:)Excuse me?
Zack, I am Amy Farrah Fowler.
We met the other night.